

Darshan Panchasara WORDPRESS DEVELOPER

- Vinayak society, Jamkhambhalia, 361305.
- pdarshan888@gmail.com
- +91 96386 14805

PROFILE

WordPress developer with extensive experience in website management, development, SEO and PPC campaigns. Expert in all aspects of creating a WordPress website, including design, modifications, implementation. Developing engaging and interactive websites. Dedicated to offering exceptional customer service at all levels, from the initial meeting with a client to website maintenance after launch.

SKILLS

Wordpress

HTML & CSS

SEO

Javascript

PROJECTS

PHP

- penless.com
- northeasthealthdistrict.org
- cakmakpainting.com
- voltronix.com
- shangbor.org
- advancedpowering.com
- snazzymediagroup.com

WORK EXPERIENCE

SR. WORDPRESS DEVELOPER

Skynet Technologies

Mar 2023 - Sep 2023

- Have worked on many challenging tasks such as custom plugin development, wordpress core development, ADA Accessibility development, etc.
- Have enhanced the PHP codding and Core Web Vitals Skills as well as skilled in woocommerce customization.

WORDPRESS DEVELOPER & SEO

Stimulus Consultancy

Aug 2021 - Feb 2023

- Have developed multiple woocommerce sites for USA, Canada, and other clients. Have done SEO on coworking & consulting services.
- Self-taught server security in DigitalOcean & AWS.

WORDPRESS DEVELOPER & CONTENT WRITER ContentHammering Aug 2020 - Aug 2021

- Created sites in wordpress on the basis of requirements.
- Self-taught & Generated tremendous amount of content for sites & blogs.

WORDPRESS DEVELOPER & SEO

Top10Products India

Mar 2019 - Aug 2020

- Created multiple affiliation sites to offer review on Amazon/Flipkart products & generate income.
- Have done hardcore off page & on page SEO on multiple projects at that time.

EDUCATION HISTORY

Masters in

Information technology & CA May 2017 - Apr 2019

Saurashtra University

- Post Graduated in Information technology & Computer Applications.
- Gained extensive training and successfully accomplished all courses for web development.

Bachelor in Computer Application

Mar 2014 - Apr 2017

Saurashtra University

- Academic Excellence in Web Design, English and Mathematics
- President of the graphics designer student's Club Staff
- Member of the Hackathon 2014-17